Caleb Babione

11532 Hastings Ave, OK caleb.b@tutanota.com (405)686-8875

A client Support Specialist at BankOnIT, A previous intern at HobbyLobby, and a student form Canadian Valley Technology Center Specializing in Computer Information Technology, Linux, Windows, and working in groups to solve diverse problems.

Key Skills

- ❖ Information Technology
- Troubleshooting
- Microsoft, Mac, and Linux OS
- ❖ Hardware & Software Configuration
- ❖ CSS, HTML, C, C#, Java
- Server Management
- ❖ Virtual Machines
- Docker
- ❖ Active Directory
- Openshift
- ❖ Yaml
- Ansible
- ❖ Esxi
- Tail Wind and React
- Java Script, and Next.JS

Employment Experience

Linux System Admin

Hobby Lobby Corporate, Oklahoma City | May 2023 - Present

- Connect printers from all stores to an SMB directory to export the scanned files
- ❖ Learn Ansible

- SSH keys
- Cvber Security
- ❖ Networking

Client Support Specialist

BankOnIT, Oklahoma City, OK | august 2023 - present

- Answer Phone Calls assisting , and troubleshooting the client's issues.
- Ensure that policies are being followed, in accordance to BankOnIT, and policies, put in place by the FDIC, are not violated.
- Install/troubleshoot proprietary
 financial applications

Achievements

Business Professionals of America Canadian Valley Technology Center, anaheim, CA | 2023

- 3rd place in Linux Operating Systems Fundamentals in National Leadership Conference
- 3rd place in Web Design Team in National Leadership Conference

Business Professionals of America Canadian Valley Technology Center, El Reno, OK | 2022 - 2023

- 1st place in Linux Operating Systems Fundamentals in State Leadership Conference
- ❖ 5th place in server Management with Microsoft Windows Server in State Leadership Conference
- Business Professionals of America Officer - Parliamentary/Secretary

Education

Completion of Certification - Computer Information Systems - May 2023 Canadian Valley Technology Center, El Reno, OK August 2022 - May 2023

Completion of Certification - Video Game Design 1 - May 2019 Tecc East, Lewisville, TX aug 2018 -May 2019

Certifications

- ❖ CompTIA A+, 2023
- ❖ IT Specialist Cyber Security
- ❖ IT Specialist Networking